孩子们 想当年
Kids,back when we were younger
我和Marshall叔叔狂爱大学篮球赛
your Uncle Marshall and I were really into college basketball.
一年一度 "三月狂潮"席卷整栋宿舍\n(指每年三月举行的全美大学生篮球赛)
Every year,March Madness would take over the entire apartment.
这黑板是怎么回事?
Hey.What's with the blackboard?
全美大学体育联盟的晋级对战图
It's our NCAA bracket.
有大黑板才有好运气!
Big board equals big luck!
这黑板看起来很眼熟
Hey, that looks familiar
哪儿来的?
Where did you get it?
你好
Hello.
我来找我妻子Aldrin老师
Uh,I'm looking for my wife,Ms.Aldrin.
今天星期六 不上课
There's no school today.It's Saturday.
那是 我怎么可能忘记?
Of course.How could I forget?
蠢驴
Dumb ass.
有大黑板!
Big board!
才有好运气!
Big luck!
我们找到的 没啥大不了
We found it.No big deal.
言归正传
Anyway,
每年 我和Ted合伙下注
every year,Ted and I go in together
把钱押在史坦顿岛的赌局
on this big money pool out in Staten Island.
优胜者能得到
Yeah.The winner gets
塞满帆布袋的10万块美金
$100,000 stuffed in a duffel bag.
而且帆布袋是附送的哦
And you get to keep the duffel bag.
你们俩干嘛非得跟自己过不去?
Why do you guys put yourselves through this?
你们压根儿就没赢过
You lose every year.
那是因为
That's because
过去只是揣测
in the past,we were just guessing.
今年 我们看遍所有比赛
This year,we watched every game,
对比个人成绩表 追踪受伤队员
read box scores,tracked injuries.
这不只是"三月狂潮"
This isn't March Madness.
更是"三月谨小慎微思潮"
This is March Meticulously Thought-outness.
你押的球队20分钟前输了
Your team lost 20 minutes ago.
我没想到他们今天有比赛
I didn't know they were playing today.
没事吧 Barney?
You okay,Barney?
最近有点莫名其妙
Something strange is going on.
我去五金店晃荡
I was down at the hardware store
寻找下手机会
trying to get a little somethin' somethin'.
等等 你跑到五金店
Wait.You go to the hardware store
淘美女?
to pick up girls?
世界上有4种女人
There are four kinds of women
会独自去五金店
who go to the hardware store by themselves.
那是当然
Of course there are.
单身的 刚失恋的 刚离婚的
Single,recently single,recently divorced,
和愿意让我看的同性恋者
lesbian who will let me watch.
你是邪恶的化身
You could not be more evil.
抱歉 是5种
Sorry.Five.
还有刚守寡的
Recently widowed.
我和一个女孩聊得正欢
So,I'm talking to this girl...
我相信他找到了更好的归宿
Look,I'm sure he's in a better place.
现在该帮你找一架更稳固的梯子
Now let's find you a sturdier ladder.
我不过走开一小会儿就...
I was only gone for a second when...
看 防滑梯
See?Skid-proof.
昨天同样的戏码在宠物店上演
The same thing happened at the pet store yesterday.
宠物店?
Pet store?
"二十多岁的单身女郎"
Single girl,mid-twenties,
"希望找小狗当替代品"
looking for a canine replacement
"填补被男友抛弃的空缺"
for the boyfriend who just dumped her.
"结果 却发现了Barney"
Instead,finds Barney.
上帝保佑你 Ted
God bless you,Ted.
你看了我的博客
You're reading my blog.
上班无聊至极
I'm really bored at work.
我想骂你的前男友是条狗
I'd call your ex a dog,
但这对"小瓢虫"狗狗是种侮辱
but that would be an insult to little Ladybug here.
我等不及要带她回家了
Oh,I want to take her home right now.
等Barney叔叔给她买个咀嚼玩具先
Not without a chew toy from Uncle Barney first.
我回来的时候
And when I got back...
不好意思 我禁不住宠坏她
I'm sorry,I'm already spoiling her
看到"未经雕琢的钻石"\n(与宠物护理机构Diamond in the Ruff谐音)
But diamond in the rough
你的心都软了吧?
Could your heart just melt?
混蛋!
Jerk!
怪异 对吧?
Weird,right?
上星期同样的戏码在博物馆上演
Yeah.The same thing happened last week at the museum.
Lily 你先来
Ooh,ooh,ooh!Lily.
你装成痛苦挣扎的年轻艺术家
You pretend to be a struggling young artist
在寻找新灵感
who needs a new muse.
不对
No.
- Marshall\n-Marshall. -You're a millionaire art thief
- 你是个百万名画大盗
正在踩点
casing the joint for a thrill
寻求金钱满足不了的刺激感!
money can no longer give you!
不对
Oh.No.
Robin\nRobin.
你即将失明
You're going blind,
试图在黑暗降临之前
and you're trying to soak up all the beauty
牢记世上所有的美丽
in the world before the darkness descends.
答对!
Bingo!
我和这女孩聊得正欢
So,I was talking to this girl.
目前 大概是83%的失明度
At this point,about 83%.
很快 助听器就是我仅有的途径了
Soon,these audio guides will be all that I have left.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
天啊 你好美
My God,you are beautiful.
不如我给你找一副耳机
How about I get you a headset
让你也试试用耳朵"看"世界?
so you can see with your ears like I do?
我顶多离开20秒
I couldn't have been gone more than 20 seconds,
回来时...
but when I came back...
我还热爱伟大艺术的气息
Hmm.You know,I also love the smell of great art.
这一而再 再而三是怎么回事?
Why does this keep happening?
也许你的说谎技巧没有你想象得高
Maybe you're not as good a liar as you think you are.
是吗?
Oh,really?
那我怎么没有因为作伪证而坐牢?
Then why am I not in prison for perjury?
不谈工作
But I don't want to talk about work.
这事儿有点不对劲儿
Something weird is going on here.
第二天晚上就更奇怪了
But the next night got even weirder.
Alan Alda\nAlan Alda.
是Alan Alda
It was Alan Alda.
你绝不会相信刚刚发生的事
You never gonna believe what just happened
两分钟前
那人是谁 演过《陆军野战医院》的?
Who was that,um,guy from Mash?
那个主角 叫什么来着?
The main guy.What...?
豪凯的扮演者
Hawkeye from Mash.
我怎么能想不起来?
How can I be blanking on this?
Alan Alda?\nAlan Alda?
不是
No.
给你几句忠告
Hey,a word of advice?
刚才跟你聊天的人 Barney Stinson
That guy you were talking to,Barney Stinson--
看似帅气迷人
I know he seems charming,
但他故献殷勤
but he's just saying whatever it takes
不过是想引诱你上床
to get in your pants.
跟Barney上床是我这辈子犯过最严重的错误
Sleeping with Barney was the biggest mistake of my life.
我的天 她在哪儿?
Oh,my God.Where is she?
肯定离开了 她...
She must have left.She...
她说我勾引她?
Well,she-she said I hooked up with her?
她名字叫啥? 长什么样子?
What was her name?What did she look like?
她没说名字 金发 胸部丰满
She didn't say her name,but she had blonde hair,boobs.
有点没脑子
Kind of trashy.
目光呆滞 有点自怨自艾?
Dead in the eyes with an aura of self-loathing and despair?
- 对!\n- 她们都是如此
-Yes! -That's all of them.
好 保持冷静
Okay.Stay calm.
仔细想想
Let's think this through.
其中一个女孩
One of the girls
我始乱终弃的对象
who I lied to,seduced and abandoned
企图毁灭我的生活
is trying to ruin my life.
推断是谁应该不难
Shouldn't be too hard to figure out which one it is.
我的神哪!
Oh,dear God!
老爸老妈浪漫史 第三季第14集
这简直是恶梦!
This is a nightmare!
一个被我始乱终弃的女人
Some woman that I slept with and screwed over
企图毁灭我的生活
is trying to ruin my life.
上帝 为什么是我?
God,why is this happening to me?
这是因果报应(karma)
It's karma.
不 不是Karma\n(女朋友多到有人取这名)
Nah,it's not Karma.
她在维加斯跳脱衣舞
She's stripping in Vegas.
而且 我们说好的
Plus,we're good.
如果你想知道是谁
Look,if you want to figure out who it is,
干嘛不从查名单入手?
why don't you just start by checking your list?
名单?
My list?
兄弟 别假装你没有一张
Dude,do not pretend you're not the kind of guy
交往过的女孩名单
who keeps a list of all the girls he's slept with.
我有一张
I have one.
那是我的结婚证\n(最浪漫的回答)
It's called my marriage license.
给我们看看名单
Come on,let's see the list.
Ted 别傻了
Ted,don't be crass.
我才不会列俗气的名单
I would never demean the women
贬低和我共枕过的女人
that I've slept with by putting their names on some tawdry list.
这本剪贴簿收集了所有和我交往过的女人
This is a scrapbook of all of the women I've slept with.
在7号的剪贴簿坊做的
I made it at the Scrapbook Barn on 7th.
找Heloise 说是我介绍你去的
Ask for Heloise.Tell her I sent you.
你觉得如何 Lil?
What do you think,Lil?
认出那个罪魁祸首没?
You recognize the saboteur?
不知道 Barney
I don't know,Barney.
我只看到她的脸
I only saw her face.
她们中有几个知道自己被拍照?
How many of these girls know they're being photographed?
所有 但走时买了复制本的只有一半
All of them,but only about half buy a copy on the way out.
Barney 你永远也查不出
Oh,Barney,you're never gonna figure out
谁是那个神秘女郎
which one of these is the mystery woman.
她们都有权利恨你
All of these women have a right to hate you.
Lily 拜托 放轻松
Oh,Lily,come on,lighten up.
任何和Barney交往的女孩
I mean,any girl who's gonna be with a guy like Barney
愿意做这个和那个
and do this or that,
或这个和那个
or this and that,
或和那个的那些做这个...
or do this with those in that...
她该清楚自己的状况
I mean,she should have known what she was getting into.
正是如此
Absolutely.
而且我对这些女人的所作所为
And what I do with these women
是我和她们之间的事
should be between me and them.
还有你们
And you guys.
还有Heloise
And Heloise.
她帮我做剪纸装饰
She helped me do the decoupage.
我不知道 Barney
I don't know,Barney.
我一个也认不出来
I don't recognize any of these women.
一些小明星 一个政府官员
I mean,some minor celebrities,one government official,
还有一个似乎是全国连锁快餐店吉祥物
and what appears to be a national fast food chain mascot.
这是不可能的任务
This is impossible.
太多女孩子了
There's too many girls.
我要怎么缩小范围呢?
How the hell am I gonna narrow this down?
我的猎艳名单前64名
The top 64 women I've slept with,
分为4个赛区
split into four regions.
这场锦标赛
This tournament
将系统化地缩小范围
will systematically narrow down
找到最有理由憎恨我的女孩
which girl has the most cause to hate my guts.
战到最后的必定是罪魁祸首
Last girl standing has to be the saboteur.
绝对不行 Barney
Absolutely not,Barney.
我们不能把这些被你骗上床的女孩
We are not going to make a game out of the women
当比赛玩
you've tricked into sleeping with you.
不可能!
No way!
那个以为他只剩下12小时生命的女孩
The girl who thought he had 12 hours to live
比假求婚那个
has way more cause to ruin his life
更有动机毁灭他的生活
than the girl he fake proposed to.
就是"假求婚"女郎
It's fake proposal girl.
她连婚礼策划人都请了!
I mean,she hired a wedding planner!
是"只能再活12小时"女郎!\n那女孩买了机票和他飞到巴黎!
It's 12 hours to live!That girl flew them both to Paris!
她不过买了单程票!
Oh,she only bought him a one-way ticket!
好 大家伙! 举手表决
Okay,okay,everybody!Hands.
"只能再活12小时"!
12 hours to live!
该死!
Damn it!
好的 投票
Okay,toss up.
"以为我是乔治・波沙达"\n(纽约洋基队职棒选手)
"Thought I was Jorge Posada,"
或"你是我已逝妻子捐肾的受惠者"?
or "You have my dead wife's kidney?"
- 肾!\n- 乔治・波沙达!
-Kidney!  -Jorge Posada!
她买了洋基队季票就为看他比赛!
She bought Yankees season tickets to watch him play!
- 的确如此...\n- 那是 "已逝妻子的肾"
-That's true...  -It's "Dead wife's kidney."
我们怎么能拿来谈笑?
How are we even discussing this?
- 是"假婴儿"!\n- "海中迷失"!
-Fake baby!  -Lost at sea!
- "假婴儿"!\n- "海中迷失"!
我当时在场
I was there.
相信我
Trust me.
是"假婴儿"
It's fake baby.
剩下"甜蜜16"\n(锦标赛第二轮剩16支球队)
Down to the sweet 16.
来自西部赛区的
And coming out of the Upper West Side,we have the number
有3号种子 "以为我拥有谷歌公司"
three seed,"Girl who thought I owned Google,"
对决7号种子
up against the number seven seed,
"以为我是潜水教练"
"Girl who thought I was a scuba instructor."
肯定选"潜水教练"
You got to go scuba instructor.
开玩笑!
You're kidding me!
她得了潜水减压症呢!
She got the bends!
嗯 的确
Yeah,she did.
"邪恶双胞胎"!
Evil twin!
"挪威王子"!
Prince of Norway!
怎么可能不选"挪威王子"?!
How could it not be Prince of Norway?!
Barney 你负责加时赛
Barney,you're the tiebreaker.
我选"邪恶双胞胎"
I'm going with Evil Twin.
你开什么玩笑!
You're kidding me!
抱歉 但我的确和她上了两次床
Sorry,but I did sleep with that girl twice.
作为Barney和Larney
As Barney and Larney.
好 剩下"终极四强"
Okay,we're down to the Final Four.
如何 伙计们?
What do you think,people?
加油 刨根究底
Come on,dig deep.
我拿不定主意
Oh!I can't decide.
任何一个都有可能
It could be any one of them.
那是我教室里的黑板吗?
Is that the blackboard from my classroom?
拜托! Marshall?
Come on!Marshall?
我又累又伤心
I'm tired and sad.
Mosby?\nMosby?
我想给妈妈打个电话
I want to call my mom,
告诉她我爱她
just tell her I love her.
好吧
Okay.
这就是我们目前为止的战果
Then this is as far as we get.
"终极四强"
The Final Four.
肯定Meg Anna
It's got to be Meg,Anna,
Kate和Holly其中之一
Kate or Holly.
我们要追踪她们
We are gonna track these girls down,
你来告诉我是谁在酒吧里接近你的
and you're going to tell me which one approached you at the bar.
你们偷了我的黑板!
You guys stole my blackboard!
好 那是她的房子
Okay,there's her building.
她一出来 我就藏起来
When she comes out,I'm gonna hide,
如果你发现她是酒吧里那个女孩
and once you figure out if she's the girl from the bar,
- 我们撒腿就跑\n- 不要
-we run like hell. -No.
不要是什么意思?
What do you mean,no?
那女孩 正如"终极四强"里的所有选手
That woman,like every woman in your Final Four,
应该得到你的道歉
deserves an apology,
你不说对不起
and I'm not telling you if she's the one
我就不告诉你是不是那女孩
until hear you say,"I'm sorry."
你疯了吗? 那我岂不是要
Are you nuts?That would involve me speaking to a woman
跟上过床的女人说话
I've already had sex with,which,frankly,
这无异于给租来的车加油
is a little t like changing the oil in a rental car.
Barney 你得听我的
Barney,you're doing this.
Lily 这女孩恨我
Lily,this girl hates me.
我在一间公寓里和她上床
I hooked up with her in an apartment
骗她说房子是我的
I was pretending was my own,
向她示爱 然后把她扔在那儿
told her I loved her,and then ditched her there.
害她因为非法入侵而被捕
She got arrested for trespassing,
咬了警察 在牢里蹲了8天
bit a cop,and spent eight days in jail.
糟糕 她出来了!
Oh,crap,there she is!
她看到我会杀了我的!
If she sees me,she's gonna kill me!
好 我们就这么做 嗨 Meg!
Okay,here's what we're gonna do.Hey,Meg!
这边!
Over here!
看这是谁!
Look who it is!
你的老朋友Barney!
Yo old friend Barney!
Barney?\nBarney?
如果她杀了我 你到我房子里
If she kills me,I want you to go into my apartment,
翻出床底下的金属纤维公文包
grab the metal briefcase under my bed
丢到东河里去
and throw it in the East River.
你在这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
Meg 我们得谈谈
Look,Meg,we need to talk.
都是我的错
It was all my fault.
我知道 宝贝儿
I know it was,baby.
我的感情太强烈了
I just came on too strong.
我原谅你
And I forgive you.
我爱你
I love you.
我的神哪!
Oh,my God!
我也爱你!
I love you,too!
不对!
No!
你脑子是不是有毛病?
What's the matter with you?
放开他!
Get off of him!
不是她
Look,she's not the one,
但你还是欠她一句道...
but you still owe her an apol...
- 你记得这个女孩?\n- 嗯
-So you remember who this one is,right? -Yes.
你借用Ted的名字 装成建筑师
You told her you were Ted and that you were an architect.
对 你记不记得
Right,and if you recall,
她的电脑有网络摄像机和T1接入线\n所以我就...
her computer had a web cam and a T-1 line,so I...
我知道 Barney 你给我看了(视频)
Yeah,I know,Barney,you showed me.
那还是不算圣诞礼物
And that still doesn't count as a Christmas present.
给我过去道歉
So go over there and apologize.
她在那儿
Ah,there she is.
她拿着热咖啡
Ooh and she's holding hot coffee.
也许会往你脸上泼
Maybe she'll throw it in your face.
你乐在其中 是吧?
You're really enjoying this,aren't you?
我要做剪贴簿
I'm making a scrapbook.
Anna 嗨
Anna,hi.
看谁大驾光临啊 "建筑大亨"先生
Look who it is,Mr.Big Shot Architect.
你要是想叫我关闭网站 就甭说了
If you're here to ask me to take down the Web site,forget it.
什么网站?
What Web site?
www.Ted-Mosby是混蛋.com
Ted-Mosby-Is-A-Jerk-dot-com.
你说得对 我活该
You're right,I do deserve that.
这就是我来的目的
That's all I came here to say.
你猜怎么着?
You know what?
我不在乎谁知道
I don't care who knows about it.
大家注意了
Excuse me.Excuse me.
本人 Ted Mosby
I,Ted Mosby,
是女人眼中的混蛋
am a jerk to women.
告诉你的姐妹 你的女儿
Tell your sisters.Tell your daughters
离我远点!
to stay away!
www.Ted-Mosby是混蛋.com
Ted-Mosby-Is-A-Jerk-dot-com.
这网站的点击率随后突破40万
And that little Web site went on to get 400,000 hits.
谢谢 Barney
Thanks,Barney.
- 好 这个又是谁?\n- 她是...
Okay,which one is this again?She's...
Larney!\nLarney!
去死!
Die!
是她吗?
Is it her?
- 去死!\n- 笑一个
-Die!-Smile.
你看起来很不错
You look good.
是不是减肥了?
Have you lost weight?
剩下1号种子
We're down to the number one seed.
我就知道是Holly
I knew it was Holly.
绝对是Holly
It had to be Holly.
我祈祷不是Holly
Man,I was hoping it wasn't Holly.
Barney 听到没?
Barney,did you hear that?
有人偷我的卡车
Somebody's stealing my truck.
Barney?\nBarney?
Barney!\nBarney!
那是你犯下的最严重的罪孽
That is the worst thing you've ever done.
那是世上最严重的罪孽
That's the worst thing anyone has ever done.
但是为我自己说一句
But in my defense,
她的确很烦人
she was kind of annoying.
她会杀了你
She's gonna kill you.
- Barney\n- Holly\n-Barney. -Holly.
Mark 出来一下
Mark,come over here.
Barney 这是我未婚夫Mark
Barney,this is my fiance. Mark.
Barney?\nBarney?
把她扔在树林里那个Barney?
You're the Barney who ditched her in the woods?
你不生Barney的气?
So you're not mad at Barney?
你不要他道歉?
Don't you want an apology?
坦白认错?
An admission of guilt?
至少把卡车要回来?
Your truck back?
不 过去的就让它过去吧
No,whatever happened was in the past.
Mark是我的现在和将来
Mark is my present and my future.
如果你在树林里抛弃Holly
And if you ditching Holly in the woods
让她看清你们的真面目
made her stop running around with guys like you,
那么 干杯吧
then cheers.
好吧
Well then,
敬最后一个被蚊子咬的
to the last Fourth of July weekend
7月4日纪念周末
I'll spend getting eaten alive by mosquitoes.
7月4日?
Fourth of July?
我们6月就开始交往了
We started dating in June.
我们毁了他们的生活
We ruined their lives.
最糟糕的是
And the worst part of it
你压根儿没道歉
is that you didn't apologize to any of those women.
不对 最糟糕的是
No,the worst part is that
我们还不知道追踪者是谁
we still have no idea who my stalker is.
那是你方法不对头
Well,that's because you're going about this all wrong.
为啥要追赶一个跟踪你的人?
I mean,why chase someone who's following you?
你只需要
All you need to do
去酒吧里 找人搭讪
is go down to the bar,hit on someone,
静待她的出现
and wait until she turns up.
这主意不错
That's not a bad idea.
我假扮被你搭讪的女孩
I'll pretend to be the girl that you're hitting on.
说不好 一个说谎时咯咯笑的女人
I don't know.That's a lot riding on a girl
不大牢靠
who giggles when she lies.
我没有
I do not.
你有没有试过在吃排骨的时候睡着?
Have you ever fallen asleep while eating ribs?
没有
No.
听着 我能行的 好吗?
Look,I can do this,okay?
不然你怎么查出那个神秘女郎
I mean,how else are you going to find out who this girl is.
我加入
I'm in.
嗯 计划是这样的
Okay,here's how it's gonna work.
现在 Lily
Now,Lily,
她知道你长什么样子
she knows what you look like,
你就在点唱机旁边晃荡
so just hang out at the jukebox,
尽量低调
and don't draw any attention to yourself.
你们坐小隔间里
And the guys will be in the booth,
假装在聊天
just pretending to have a normal conversation.
聊天 我们得聊天 说话
Talking,we should be talking.Words.
说几句话
Here are words.
咋这么难?
Why is this so hard?
笑!
Laughter!
紧接着我进来了
And then I'll come in,
性感得要命
looking hot as all hell.
你真漂亮
Wow,you are gorgeous.
神哪 我知道很烂
Oh,God,I know that's awful.
- 只是....\n- 嘘 走开
-I just,uh.... -Shh,go away.
一会儿回来
But come back later.
然后Barney就发动攻势
And then Barney  will make his move.
嗨 美女 你好吗?
Hey,there,how are you doing?
我很好 Barney
Fine,Barney.
我是说
I mean,um,
我很好 陌生人
fine,stranger.
你演技实在很烂
Wow,you really are awful at this,aren't you?
把你的手
Get your hand
从我大腿上挪开 Barney
off my thigh,Barney.
做戏要做全套
It's supposed to look like
我在勾引你 Robin
we're about to hook up,Robin.
我很好奇
You know I'm curious.
你说了什么
What do you say to these girls
把她们骗回家?
to get them to come home with you?
通常情况下
Usually I just
我只要倾斜身子在她们耳边轻声细语
lean in and whisper this one thing in their ear.
你有点兴奋了吧?
You're a little turned on right now,aren't you?
没有
No.
瞧 有人盯着我们看
Oh.Look,somebody's watching us.
转移到厕所去
Make your move to the bathroom.
我现在去上厕所
Uh,I'm going to go to the bathroom now,
等我回来 一起去我家嘿咻
but,uh,when I come back we'll go to my place and have sex.
兄弟 兄弟 看看
Dude,dude,dude,look.
有个金发美女靠近Robin 我们行动
Blonde girl heading over to Robin right now.We are go.
我的手不知道该怎么摆
I don't know what to do with my hands.
正常情况下我的手怎么摆?
What do I normally do with my hands?
Barney\nBarney.
我复制了"对战图"
I brought a copy of the bracket.
是哪一个?
Which one is she?
我认不出来
I don't recognize her.
她不在前64强里
She's not on the Top 64.
居然不在"对战图"上
Not even on bracket.
不知从哪里冒出来的灰姑娘\n(即俗称的黑马)
Cinderella story comes out of nowhere to win the whole thing.
这真是温暖人心
That'll warm your heart.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
我居然认不出她是谁
I don't even recognize her.
我不记得你
I don't remember you.
我花了两天时间
I've spent the last two days trying to remember
回忆每个交往过的女孩
every girl that I've slept with and all the horrible things
和我的所作所为
that I have done to them.
我有些行径令人发指
And I have done some horrible things.
有一次 我把一个女的给卖了
I mean,at one point,I'm pretty sure I sold a woman.
我没有谈买卖
I didn't speak the language,
只是握了一个家伙的手
but I shook a guy's hand,
他给我一串默西迪丝车的钥匙\n我就把她扔在那儿了
he gave me the keys to a Mercedes,and I left her there.
我制作一本剪贴簿
I'm the guy who keeps a scrapbook
收集和我交往过的女孩
of all of the women I have slept with,
但我绝对没想到
but I never thought I was the guy
我会想不起和我上过床的女孩
who would sleep with a girl and not even remember her.
所以我真心诚意地
So from the bottom of my heart,
为我的所作所为
for whatever I did to you,
向你道歉
I apologize.
Barney!\nOh,Barney!
我真为你感到骄傲
Oh,I'm so proud of you.
不是她
That's not her.
- 很抱歉\n- 什么? 什么?
-I'm so sorry.-What?What?
Barney 不好意思 那是我的同事Sally
Barney,I'm sorry,that's my friend Sally from work.
我们恰好碰见的
We just ran into each other.
那我白道歉了?
So I apologized for nothing?
是 但那是很好的道歉
Yes,but it was a great apology.
也是剪贴簿的完美结局
And a perfect way to end my scrapbook.
我给这张照片起名叫"Barney的救赎"
I'm going to call this photo "Barney's Redemption."
你能不能别对我竖中指?
Could you stop giving me the finger?
* 闪亮时刻 *
* That one shining moment
* 你展翅翱翔 *
* You reached for the sky
* 你知道的闪亮时刻 *
* One shining moment you knew
* 闪亮时刻 *
* One shining moment
* 你勇于尝试 *
* You were willing to try
* 闪亮时刻 *
* One shining moment
最后 Barney终于找到
Eventually,  Barney did figure out
那位神秘女郎 这个我们稍后再说
who the mysterious girl was. But we on that later
2008年3月21日 Barney的博客\n有时我们在寻觅中得到意外的发现
尽管没有找到神秘女郎...
我却发现了一个关于自己的重要事实
Barney 睡觉吧
Barney, come back to bed
你明天还要发射航天飞机
You have a shuttle launch tomorrow.
那颗飞往曼哈顿的小行星
And that asteroid that's headed for Manhattan,
可不会自我毁灭哦
It's not gonna destroy itself.
我的魅力无法挡